http://www.friendsinbusiness.com/privacypolicy.shtml

Friends In Business & Scams 101Home PagePrivacy Policy: FriendsInBusiness.com
I Do HerebySolemnly Swear
on a stack of yummy king-size Hershey barsand a private place to eat them
that FriendsInBusiness.com will NEVER sell, rent, lease, or give your name, e-mail address, or any other personal information you entrust us with to another living soul.
That's the least you need to know.
Following is our Official Privacy Policy with all the technicalities -- including what types of personal
information we might receive and/or collect here at www.FriendsInBusiness.com, how it can be used, etc.
If you need more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact me by email.
Log Files Like just about every other web site on the planet, www.FriendsInBusiness.com
makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet
protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends,
administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather
demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked
to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons www.FriendsInBusiness.com does use
cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific
information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content
based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via
their browser.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based
on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad
and content network privacy policy at the following URL -
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our
site. Our advertising partners include .......
Google Adsense
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the
advertisements and links that appear on www.FriendsInBusiness.com send directly
to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs.
Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be
used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their
advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
www.FriendsInBusiness.com has no access to or control over these cookies
that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad
servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for
instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.
www.FriendsInBusiness.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot
control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific
web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
A final note:  If you disable our cookies, the forum won't know which messages
you've already read and it will have no way to store your preferences, making your visits
less enjoyable.
Use your BACK button to continue where you left off.
